<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">AISLATECH</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="openDrawer">Open Drawer</string>
    <string name="closeDrawer">Close Drawer</string>
    <string name="home_description">
<![CDATA[
<html>
 <head></head>
 <body style="text-align:justify;color:black;">
The Association of Indian Students (AIS) has been existing on the
        campus since 1993. However, the Association was reinstated to its current form on October 02, 2000,
        with an intent to bring back the spirit of Indian-ness to the Tech campus, and has been doing consistently well ever since.
        AIS has been actively engaged in making Indian students at Louisiana Tech University feel "at home". </br> </br>The involvement of
        AIS with Indian students starts with guiding new applicants with necessary information pertaining to the University,
        informing prospective students about the academic programs and research at the University, guiding students through
        the visa procedures, and extends to picking up students from the nearby Monroe Regional Airport, accommodating them
        temporarily at current students apartments while guiding them in finding accommodation for themselves, apart from
        conducting various events on the campus, sometimes in conjunction with the International Student Office (ISO),
        International Student Association (ISA), and the India Association of North Louisiana (IANL). Through all these,
        the Association of Indian Students works hand in hand with the ISO, while also helping the Office through orientation
        for Indian students on the campus.
 </body>
</html>
]]>
        </string>
    <string name="transition_name_name">transition:NAME</string>
    <string name="transition_name_circle">transition:CIRCLE</string>
    <string name="transition_name_phone">transition:PHONE</string>

</resources>
